It is Our Great honor to present the First Ever Nickelodeon lifetime achievement award
It is Our Great honor to present the First Ever Nickelodeon lifetime achievement award
to a man who's been making All of Us laugh For the past two decades dan
to a man who's been making All of Us laugh For the past two decades dan
Schneider Come on Give Up the
Schneider Come on Give Up the
Juice you want to get slapped with the sausage
Juice you want to get slapped with the sausage
sure to say ni things about Cuz I will tase her If necessary
sure say ni things about Cuz I will tase her If necessary
That's going to get on TV That's going to get on
That's going to get on TV That's going to get on
TV Why are you sitting on the floor of the set be essentially
TV Why are you sitting on the floor of the set be essentially
tortured
tortured
Oh
Ay
yes, what we just saw in the intro is very shady, we are not going to deny it but it is even murkier
sí lo que acabamos de ver en la intro es muy turbio no lo vamos a negar pero más turbio
after knowing that these things that you have just seen were seen on television and that
todavía es después de saber que estas cosas que acabáis de ver se vieron en televisión y que
many more things happened behind the camera for two decades, surely many of the
sucedieron muchas más cosas detrás de cámara durante dos décadas seguramente muchas de las
things that we are going to review in this video many of you have seen when They were broadcast but
cosas que vamos a repasar en este vídeo muchos de ustedes las hayáis visto cuando se emitieron pero
since you were children or teenagers Well, maybe you didn't see it with evil and for any
como erais niños o erais adolescentes Pues a lo mejor no lo visteis con maldad y para cualquier
kid Maybe it went unnoticed to realize the seriousness of the matter behind these
chaval A lo mejor pasó desapercibido el darse cuenta de la gravedad del asunto tras estas
scenes in the early 2000s Nickelodion was the most beloved network By both children and
escenas a principios de los años 2000 nickelodion era la cadena más querida tanto por los niños como
young people, their cartoons were the most watched during the day, the ones with the largest audience,
por los jóvenes sus dibujos animados eran los más vistos durante el día los que más audienci tenían
even completely eating up Cartoon Network and the Disney Channel
incluso comiéndose por completo a Cartoon Network y al mismísimo Disney Channel caricaturas en el
itself. Teen comedies were becoming
horario infantil algún programa por la tarde y en sus noches sus comedias adolescentes se hacían
more and more relevant. You will surely remember shows like Clarisa Kenan and Kel or Drake and Jos, which is a
cada vez más relevantes seguramente recordará show como Clarisa Kenan y Kel o Drake y Jos que es una
series that will certainly gain a lot of importance at the end of this video. So I invite you to
serie que por cierto cobrará mucha importancia al final de este vídeo Así que te invito que te
stay until the end. I am going to talk to you about a guy who is currently unpunished a guy who has been
quedes hasta el final voy a hablaros de un tipo que actualmente está impune un tipo que ha sido
accused on numerous occasions of child abuse and behaving in a very shady manner with
acusado en numerosas ocasiones de abuso infantil y de comportarse de manera muy turbia con con
minors, abusing power because he was Nickelodeon's most important producer for
menores haciendo un abuso de poder porque fue el productor más importante de Nickelodeon durante
many years in the golden age dan sneider es a producer, screenwriter, director and writer
muchísimos años en la época dorada dan sneider es un productor guionista director y escritor
who came to Nickelodeon in 1993. He previously had a career as an actor in the mid-
que llegó a Nickelodeon en 1993 previamente Tuvo una carrera como actor A mediados de los
80s where he played some supporting roles in films, the best known and most
años 80 donde hizo algunos papeles secundarios en películas siendo el más conocido y el más
remembered being Ricky in the film Better of the One. comes to translate better dead if you want
recordado el de Ricky en la película better of the que se viene a traducir más vale muerto si queréis
a preview and ask me what is my opinion regarding this guy I would clearly describe him
un adelanto y me preguntáis Cuál es mi opinión respecto a este tipo claramente lo describiría
as the title I gave to this video the Nickelodeon Predator a guy with
como el título que le he puesto a este vídeo el Depredador de Nickelodeon un tipo con sentimientos
disgusting feelings towards the girls he worked with and that he had a certain taste for feet and I'm not
asquerosos hacia las niñas con las que trabajaba y que tenía cierto gusto por los pies y no me
referring to refrigerator ice cream, his last post on Instagram is a posthumous message to Mafi Perry,
refiero al helado de frigo su última publicación en instagram es un mensaje póstumo a mafi Perry
that is, Cherle, for his friends and never Better said after his death, remembering that he starred in
o sea cherle para los amigos y nunca Mejor dicho después de su muerte recordando que protagonizó
a comedy with him early 90s before he came to his very famous series
una comedia con él a principios de los años 90s antes de que este llegara a su famosísimo serie
yerel What's up my people welcome one more day to the Channel I am Javi oliveira if you didn't know me
yerel Qué pasa mi gente bienvenidos un día más al Canal Soy Javi oliveira si no me conocías
I invite you to subscribe to the channel it is completely free and here we will deal with
te invito a que te suscribas al canal es completamente gratuito y aquí trataremos
all the viral topics Internet curiosities and very powerful sauces If you want to find out
todos los temas virales curiosidades de internet y salseos muy potentes si quieres enterarte de
everything in the most entertaining way possible and you like this type of content, I invite you to
todo de la forma más entretenida posible y te gusta este tipo de contenido te invito a
subscribe and press the like button so that YouTube always recommends
que te suscribas y a que pulses el botón de like para que YouTube te recomiende siempre
my videos in this video as Well, the title says, I'm going to talk to you about the predator of Nikelodion Dan
mis vídeos en este vídeo como bien Dice el título os voy a hablar del depredador de nikelodion dan
Schneider whose stories of alleged sexual abuse of minors and abuse of power for having
Schneider cuyas historias de presuntos abusos sexuales a menores y abuso de poder por tener
that position on the very famous television network is coming to light through a new documentary
ese Cargo en la famosísima cadena de televisión está saliendo a flote por un nuevo documental
that is being broadcast right now. While you're watching this video I think they're on
que se está emitiendo ahora mismo mientras que estáis viendo este vídeo Creo que van
about the second episode And so far what we have is a bomb And what do you want me to tell you? I
como por el segundo episodio Y hasta ahora lo que tenemos es una bomba Y qué queréis que os diga yo
greatly respect the presumption of innocence. This guy has had four
respeto mucho la presunción de inocencia este tipo ha tenido en su equipo a cuatro pedófilos
convicted pedophiles working with him on his team. and he has not been convicted at the moment, some of the actresses who
condenados trabajando con él y él no ha sido condenado de momento algunas de las actrices que
have worked on the network claim that it is because of the power it has, not with the justice system but with shutting up
han trabajado en la cadena afirman que es por el poder que tiene no con la justicia sino de callar
mouths, but really the things that we are going to see in this video simply with the scenes that You have
bocas pero realmente las cosas que vamos a ver en este vídeo simplemente con las escenas que habéis
seen in the intro the things he does to the boys and especially to the girls. I think
visto en la intro las cosas que les hacer a los chavales y sobre todo a las chavalas yo creo que
they are more than enough to think that this guy would surely be on Jeffrey Esting's list.
son más que suficientes para pensar que este tío seguramente estaría en la lista de Jeffrey esting
Get comfortable and pay attention to the video at the 1988 Kid Choy Awards. He meets a
poneros comoos y atentos al vídeo en los premios Kid choy Awards de 1988 conoce a un empleado de
Nickelodeon employee named Alv Hit who would end up being president of the network and being hired
Nickelodeon llamado alv hit quien terminaría siendo presidente de la cadena y contratándose
here. I really feel like taking a break to point out this marriage, or really,
aquí realmente se me apetece hacer un parón para señalar a este matrimonio o sea realmente
surely this one? Madam, you have more context of the story and you know many more clues than us
seguramente esta señora tenga más contexto de la historia y sepa muchos más indicios que nosotros
and you will have seen many more scenes than we are going to see in this video. How is it possible
y habrá visto muchas más escenas de las que vayamos a ver en este vídeo cómo es posible
that you are still married to this day? You just reminded me and I can't think of anything else. that
que a día de hoy continúe casado me acaba de recordar y no se me ocurre otra cosa que a
Jlin Maxwell putting up with everything Jeffrey Epstein did and covering up his moves. Really, if you
jlin Maxwell aguantando todo lo que hacía Jeffrey epstein y cubriendo sus movidas Realmente si tú
know 10% of the context and the things that have come out of this guy, it is very unlikely that she will want
conoces un 10% del contexto y de las cosas que han salido de este tipo es muy improbable que quiera
to continue not being married to him but deleting all your history of what you have experienced with him in
a seguir ya no casada con él sino borrando todo tu historial de lo que Has vivido con él en los
recent years and perhaps decades some very strong rumors and accusations have been made about dan
últimos años y tal vez décadas algunos rumores y acusaciones muy fuertes se han hecho sobre dan
sneider accusations on social networks of some actors and anonymous confessions have caused
sneider acusaciones en redes sociales de algunos actores y confesiones anónimas han hecho que se
dan's name to be questioned in some forums and networks such as Twitter and in some books without
cuestione el nombre de dan en algunos foros y redes como en Twitter y en algunos libros sin
naming him directly but making the allusion very clear, they have accused him of alleged labor abuse,
nombrarlo directamente pero quedando muy clara la alusión lo han acusado de presunto abuso laboral
alleged sexual abuse, fetishism and even mistreatment and let us not forget all this
presunto abuso sexual fetichismo e incluso de malos tratos y que no se nos olvide todo esto
broadcast on television before everyone's eyes. the planet during the golden era of
retransmitido en televisión ante la mirada de todo el planeta durante la era dorada de la televisión
cable television between 1996 and 2016 Nickel Odeion was the clear dominant, consistently surpassing
por cable entre 1996 y 2016 nickel odeion fue el claro dominante superando consistentemente
the titan Disney Channel itself and even Cartoon Network almost all the time,
durante todo ese tiempo al mismísimo titán Disney Channel E incluso a Cartoon Network casi todo el
creating a perfect combination between cartoons created by themselves and
tiempo creando una combinación perfecta entre dibujos animados creados por ellos mismos y
teen comedies SpongeBob SquarePants Hey Arnold Jimmy Neutron among many others are
comedias de adolescentes Bob Esponja los rugas Hey Arnold Jimmy neutron entre otras muchas más son
series that I'm 100% sure, even if you haven't seen any episode, I'm completely sure that
series que seguro al 100% aunque no hayas visto ningún episodio estoy completamente seguro de que
absolutely no one watching this video has ever heard any of these names
absolutamente nadie que esté viendo Este vídeo no he escuchado nunca alguno de estos nombres
It especially competed with Disney Channel since it was in the fight with it, fighting
Especialmente competía con Disney Channel ya que este estaba en la lucha con él haciéndole un pulso
for the teenage audience, trying to bring to its network the same type of humor, the same type
por el público adolescente intentando traer a su cadena el mismo tipo de humor el mismo tipo
of teenage series from which many artists of the day came out between the two networks. today
de series teenagers de las cuales entre las dos cadenas salieron muchísimas artistas del día de
and well-known people like Miley saurus and no it is not a dinosaur called Miley tini in her
hoy y gente muy conocida como Miley saurus y no no es un dinosaurio que se llama Miley tini en su
time Violeta sendall Ariana Grande who will have a lot of prominence in this video the formula that
tiempo Violeta sendall Ariana Grande que tendrá mucho protagonismo en este vídeo la fórmula que
always worked for the Channel and in most cases for many Of the boys who participated
siempre le funcionó al Canal y en la mayoría de casos para muchos de los chicos que participaban
in the series, acting in this type of show was fulfilling a dream, however, there was an exception
en las series actuar en este tipo de show era cumplir un sueño sin embargo había una excepción
without anyone knowing Janette McCurdy. When we talk about this type of accusations from
sin que nadie lo supiera Janette Mccurdy cuando se habla de este tipo de acusaciones de gente
such famous people, we obviously have to do it very carefully and be very cautious, we have seen on
tan famosa evidentemente tenemos que hacerlo bajo mucho cuidado y ser muy prudentes hemos visto en
some occasions, such as in the case of Michael Jackson, as they have always pointed out, of having
algunas ocasiones como por e en el caso de Michael Jackson como siempre lo han señalado de tener
shady things and turning out to be innocent with people convicted today for defaming, however in
cosas turbias y resultar siendo inocente con gente condenada a día de hoy por difamar sin embargo en
this case, unlike the case of Michael Jackson, quite the opposite, as the decades go by,
este caso a diferencia del caso de Michael Jackson todo lo contrario conforme van pasando las décadas
what comes out on the table is more and more evidence that is quite likely to be
lo que van saliendo sobre la mesa son más y más pruebas que tienen bastante probabilidad de su
true and that not even anyone is coming out to deny the truth, that is, this guy has not defended himself
veracidad y que ni siquiera nadie está saliendo a desmentir laas o sea este tipo no se ha defendido
on any occasion against At the time of none of the accusations that have been made against him, Michael Jackson
en ninguna ocasión de momento de Ninguno de los señalamientos que le han hecho Michael Jackson
on any occasion even rejected judicial agreements that could have saved him headaches
en alguna ocasión incluso rechazó pasó acuerdos judiciales que podrían haberle ahorrado dolores de
to go to the end of the lawsuits and prove his innocence in fact to dan Schneider
cabeza para llegar hasta el final de los pleitos y demostrar su inocencia de hecho a dan Schneider
have even gone so far as to link him with Harvey Wasin himself, who is currently convicted
han llegado incluso a vincularlo con el mismísimo Harvey wasin que se encuentra ahora mismo condenad
of sexual assault, rape in the third degree and is sentenced to more than 30 years in
simo por agresiones sexuales violaciones en tercer grado y está condenado como a más de 30 años de
prison, has a sentence of 23 years and another of 16. They give what he did on his Twitter account in the
prisión tiene una condena de 23 años y otra de 16 dan lo que hizo en su cuenta de Twitter en el
At the time when they began to link him to this director, what he did was delete any tweet
momento en el que empezaron a vincularlo con este director lo que hizo fue eliminar cualquier tweet
he had in relation to him and for some reason delete any publication he had on
que tuviera en relación con él y eliminar por algún motivo cualquier publicación que tuviera en
Twitter related to feet. I think that no matter how much presumption of innocence we always want to have
Twitter relacionada con pies Yo creo que por más presunción de inocencia que queramos tener siempre
for flag is more than evident that the foot fetish issue and You are going to see Many feet in
por bandera es más que evidente que lo del tema fetiche por los pies y Vais a ver Muchos pies en
This video is not something that can be ruled out or hidden and that the guy has
este vídeo no es una cosa que se pueda descartar ni que se pueda ocultar y que el tipo tiene
shady behavior either to put you in context a little in case there is someone who is not able
conductas turbias tampoco para poneros un poco en contexto por si hay alguien que no es capaz
to perceive the power that a person like this has, we have to point out that this man has had
de percibir el poder que tiene una persona como esta tenemos que señalar que este hombre ha tenido
numerous successes on television in teenage series that we are talking about a Niche in
numerosos exitazos en televisión en series de adolescentes que estamos hablando de un Nicho en
which it is not easy to succeed because it is a very specific audience and this gentleman has managed to have
el que no es fácil triunfar porque es un público muy específico y este caballero ha llegado a tener
series and episodes in them with more than 13 million viewers in its broadcast and then repeat the
series y episodios en ellas con más de 13 millones de espectadores en su emisión y luego repetir el
episode at another time and have six more. We are talking about an outrage. We are talking about
capítulo en otro horario y tener seis más estamos hablando de una barbaridad estamos hablando de
the main television networks in my country. They have not had that even in the most golden thing
que las principales cadenas de televisión de mi país No han tenido eso ni en lo más dorado que
they have done in recent times is that I can't even tell you how many decades. I don't know if maybe in some
hayan hecho en los últimos es que no sé decirte ni Cuántas décadas no sé si a lo mejor en alguna
football thing at a World Cup or something like that, making series for teenagers between
cosa de fútbol de algún mundial o algo por el estilo hacer series para adolescentes entre
13 and 16 years old is a very difficult challenge. The audience is kids who want to feel like adults. We have to.
13 y 16 años es un reto muy difícil la audiencia son chicos que se quieren sentir adultos Hay que
give them a little of that but you also have to be clear about the limits and try not to go overboard because
darles un poco de eso pero también hay que tener claros los límites e intentar no pasarlo porque
the people who watch the program are still minors, as I'm going to show you, Dan Sneider clearly
la gente que ve el programa siguen siendo menores como os voy a demostrar dan sneider claramente los
went over them while the Nickelodeon series stood out for having more humor. acid its
pasaba mientras que las series de Nickelodeon destacaban por tener un humor más más ácido su
competition More direct Disney Channel was betting on something whiter and it did not cross
competencia Más directa Disney Channel apostaba por algo más blanco y que ni de coña traspasaba
that line even though Disney had quite successful programs, it was forced on some occasions
esa línea aunque Disney tenía programas bastante exitosos se vio en la obligación en alguna ocasión
to plagiarize a little bit of a script, thereby bringing a constant clash between the two companies
de plagiar un poquillo algún guion trayendo con esto un pique constante entre las dos compañías
in which they even threw what we call today on the internet as a bit of a steak.
en la que incluso se tiraron lo que hoy en día llamamos en internet como un poquillo de bifeo
They have seen everything with Teri on Dingo Channel. No, it's disgusting because last night my brother was watching it and
han visto todo con teri en dingo Channel No qué asco porque anoche mi hermano lo estaba viendo y
they copied a segment of his show, what did one of the actors do? he pressed a button he heard
copiaron un segmento de su programa qué hicieron uno de los actores presionó un botón escucho
improvised jump they put on music a lot of lights and they started jumping like crazy it's exactly the same
salto improvisado pusieron música muchas luces y empezaron a saltar como locos es Exactamente igual
as improvised dancing Well yes I noticed it they copied Carly they should do something about it yes
a baile improvisado Pues sí lo noté copiaron a Carly deberían hacer algo al respecto sí
they should I hate dingo Channel shows it was common in the shows where This man
deberían odio los programas de dingo Channel era habitual en los programas en los que este señor
was in charge of watching some scenes with teenage girls who used to have very
tenía el mando ver algunas escenas con chicas adolescentes que solían tener pantalones muy
short pants Ariana Grande is surely the one with the strangest clips and what catches my
cortos Ariana Grande sea seguramente la que tiene clips más extraños y lo que me llama
attention about her is not only that she has it, I understand that at the moment maybe You don't realize
la atención de ella no solamente es que lo tenga entiendo que en el momento a lo mejor no te des
the seriousness of what they are doing to you But as the years have passed, what
cuenta de la gravedad de lo que te están haciendo Pero conforme han ido pasando Los años lo que me
surprises me a lot is that this girl is one of the few who has not come out to report it, Dan discovered her
extraña mucho es que esta chica sea de las pocas que no ha salido a denunciarlo dan la descubrió
at the age of 13, she had her in a program and then he made her the protagonist of another, we are talking about
a los 13 años la tuvo en un programa y luego la volvió protagonista de otro estamos hablando de
Dan Sneider's humor, in my opinion, as the years went by, it became more murky
que el humor de dan sneider en mi opinión conforme iban pasando los años se iba volviendo más turbio
and Ana Grande was right in this guy's last period as a director, so he had to The
y haría Ana grande estuvo justo en la última época de este tío como director por lo tanto le tocó lo
most important thing is to tell me what you think of this click that I am going to put on the screen. Also in
más grueso decirme ustedes qué pensáis de este click que os voy a poner en pantalla además en
this video I want to be very active in the chat and if you see double meaning in these words Or is it that
este vídeo quiero muy activos en el chat y si veis doble sentido en estas palabras O es que
I am very poorly thought out soing W somebody bring me the oan no One Would Ever Say that Why Because if
yo soy muy mal pensado soing W somebody bring me the oan no One would Ever Say that Why Because if
you soaking wet ands you want For To is More Than person Hey, I don't know, maybe they were
you soaking wet ands you want For To is More Than person Oye que no lo sé que a lo mejor le estaban
giving this script to this little girl because in the house where her character lived there was no
dando este guion a esta chiquilla porque en la casa donde vivía su personaje no había
roof like I have already told you that this man has a certain attraction to feet and later in
techo como ya os he comentado este hombre tiene cierta atracción por los pies y más adelante en
the video you will see that it is common to see a lot of them. In his children's programs,
el vídeo Vais a ver que es habitual ver un montón de ellos En sus programas infantiles
anything he found in the script that could serve as an excuse for someone
cualquier cosa que encontraba en el guion que le pudiera servir como excusa para que alguien
to you take off your socks and with that I could get a close-up of the pinreles I
se quitas los calcetines y que con eso pudiera conseguir un primer plano de los pinreles la
took advantage of what I'm going to tell you next I don't even know how
aprovechaba lo que os voy a poner a continuación no sé ni cómo
to describe it and another one
describirlo y otro
as a father one of the first things that come to mind and I can't To prevent this from happening,
más como padre una de las primeras cosas que se me vienen a la mente y no puedo evitar que sea
when this girl is recording these scenes, the parents are not there, that is,
así es cuando esta chiquilla está grabando estas escenas no están los padres o sea literalmente
we are literally talking about a minor. Parents are supposed to supervise their
estamos hablando de una menor se supone que los padres tienen que supervisar el trabajo de los
children's work, and in the event that there is first a script, when this girl was reading the script
hijos y en el caso que primero haya un guion cuando esta muchacha estaba leyendo el guion
His mother hasn't even taken a look because I understand that when a person reads this script,
su madre no ha echado ni un vistazo porque yo entiendo que una persona cuando lee este guion
who probably has to describe even the gestures, he wouldn't think that he was talking
que seguramente tenga que describir incluso los gestos no se pensaría que estaba hablando
about a McDonald's potato. No, or that he was playing at removing Mr. Potato's ears.
de una patata del McDonald's No ni de que estaba jugando a quitarle las orejitas al señor potato
I don't want someone to explain to me the intention that the director of photography had when this girl was
no que me explique alguien la intención que tenía el director de fotografía cuando esta chica estaba
doing poses like these to be broadcast, which must be repeated. It's okay to be broadcast on a
haciendo poses como estas para emitirse que hay que repetirlo vale para emitirse en un programa
children's program, it must be said that most of these clips, the ones that are most controversial, are not They broadcast
infantil hay que decir que la mayoría de estos clip los que son más polémicos no se emitían
directly on the television network but in some way they promoted it from
directamente en la cadena de televisión sino que de alguna forma lo promocionaban desde la
TV but published them on their website. I have not been able to verify at this time if perhaps
tele pero las publicaban en su página web no he podido comprobar ya en esta época si a lo mejor
it was to attract an audience to the website because later within the website they sold some
era para atraer público a la página web porque ya luego dentro de la página web vendían algún
type of product or whatever, which I imagine would be like that in the case of the series Victorious,
tipo de producto o lo que sea que me imagino que sería así en el caso de la serie Victorious hace
the real reason why this series starring the
poco se conoció el verdadero motivo por el que fue cancelada esta serie protagonizada por la
very famous Victoria Justice, who later continued with his career as an artist and
famosísima Victoria Justice que más adelante ha continuado con su carrera como artista y
he is killing it, apparently in this case the closure had nothing to do with anything strange about
lo está petando por lo visto en este caso el cierre no tuvo nada que ver con nada raro de
Dan Sneider as a producer and screenwriter, you know because of things with double meanings and this
dan sneider como productor y guionista ya sabéis por cosas con doble sentido y este
type of things that we just saw, but more well because the actors were quite
tipo de cosas que acabamos de ver sino que más bien porque los actores estaban bastante
revolutionized and were generating a lot of controversy and controversy outside
revolucionados y estaban generando bastante polémica y controversia en lo que es afuera
the series. What does this mean? Well, they were caught on several occasions having sex, apparently
de la serie Qué quiere decir esto Pues que les pillaron en varias ocasiones teniendo sexo por
not only off the set but in the dressing rooms in areas At work, let's
lo visto no solamente fuera del set sino que en los camerinos en zonas de trabajo a
see, they are kids at a very bad age in which the hormones are at Flor's feet.
ver son chavales en una edad muy mala en la que las hormonas están a Flor de pie
They were even involved with drugs and things like that. In fact, even nudes
incluso estaban liados con drogas y cosas por el estilo se filtraron de hecho incluso nudes
of victories were leaked and this. Well, look at the network, you don't have any scruples. apparently not to the network
de victorias y esto Pues a la cadena fíjate tú no qué escrúpulos no a la cadena por lo visto
because she was not happy that Victoria had leaked nudes out there on the internet, if there was
pues no le hacía gracia que Victoria tuviera nudes por ahí por internet filtrados si había
any attractive photograph, she preferred to give it to the director, but well, apart from the joke, I suppose
alguna fotografía atractiva prefería que dársela al director pero bueno aparte del chiste Supongo
that being Nikelodio on a children's network in which I understand that there would be advertisers because it was not the
que siendo nikelodio en una cadena infantil en la que entiendo que habría anunciantes pues no era la
best idea for their actors and the protagonists of their series to be involved in this
mejor idea que sus actores y los protagonistas de sus series estuvieran involucrados en este
type of media controversies when we talk about sex, drugs and alcohol,
tipo de polémicas mediáticas cuando hablamos de sexo drogas y alcohol
surely
seguramente
I already told you that this decision surprises me taking into account that, for
ya te digo que a mí me extraña esta decisión teniendo en cuenta que por
example, the director He put them in situations like this one that you will see in the following
ejemplo el director los ponía en situaciones como esta que Vais a ver en el siguiente
clip in which he used the excuse of a resuscitation so that the two teenagers
clip en los que utilizaba la excusa de una reanimación para que los dos adolescentes
could make out but What does that have to do with action Ok well II lost my cellone Can you please help me
enrollen but What does that have to do with action Ok well I I lost my cellone Can you please help me
cheers pch he was really Giving me Mouth to Mouth resuscitation right was a Blue pair
cheers pch he was really Giving me Mouth to Mouth resuscitation right was a Blue pair
phone the new one And I know I Had it When I was buying a pretzel but I just I don't
phone the new one And I know I Had it When I was buying a pretzel but I just I don't
remember sir I think It's Great that you are a Uh
remember sir I think It's Great that you are a Uh
control them When I was 13 years old I still had a pass But as the kids
controlarlos cuando tenía 13 años Todavía tenía un pase Pero conforme los chavales
grew up and approached their twenties it was completely impossible and as I already
fueron creciendo y se iban acercando a la veintena de edad era completamente imposible y como ya os
told you they ended the series Yes, Dan wanted to keep Ariana Grande with whom he had a
he dicho finalizaron la serie Eso sí dan quiso conservar Ariana Grande con la que le unía una
great relationship and the very famous series of Sam and Cat arrived, starring Ariana Grande and Janette
gran relación y llegó la famosísima serie de Sam y Cat protagonizadas por Ariana Grande y Janette
Macardy. Parenthesis, I'm making an effort and I've done it. While I was preparing the video
macardy paréntesis estoy haciendo un esfuerzo y lo he hecho Mientras que preparaba el vídeo
to review well how the names are pronounced, I'm probably going to slip up in some of them, but for my
de revisar bien cómo se pronuncian los nombres seguramente en alguno voy a patinar pero por mi
effort I deserve it. your like Give it to him handsome jette macardi was one of the first to accuse dan
esfuerzo me merezco tu like Dáselo guapetón jette macardi fue una de las primeras en acusar a dan
of abuse the book he released in 2022 was very viral both on Amazon and in all bookstores
de abuso el libro que sacó en el año 2022 fue muy viral tanto en Amazon como en todas las librerías
and there was a lot of talk on the internet about the subject also in television shows it was bestseller of
y en internet se habló mucho del tema también en programas de televisión fue bestseller de
non-fiction books and the second best seller on Amazon, surpassing even novels by Colen
libros de no ficción y el segundo más vendido de Amazon superando incluso novelas de colen
Huber. In reality, it would be great to tell you a little about the context of this girl's story and
huber en realidad estaría divino comentaros un poco el contexto de la historia de esta chica y
the hard life she had before she suffered these alleged abuses. work that
de la vida tan dura que ha tenido antes de que sufriera estos supuestos abusos laborales que
she tells in that book because the girl has a context of a very complicated life, a mother who
ella relata en ese libro porque la chica tiene un contexto de una vida muy complicada una madre que
becomes very crazy, mistreats her throughout her life and it is a tremendous, very shady thing that she
se vuelve loquísima la maltrata durante toda su vida y es una cosa tremenda muy turbia de la que
If you want me to make another video, ask me in the comments box and if I see that this one
si queréis que os haga otro vídeo me lo pedís en la caja de comentarios y si veo que este
has a lot of support and that you ask me a lot in the comments and the comments where you ask me for it,
tiene mucho apoyo y que me lo pedís mucho en los comentarios y los comentarios dónde me lo pedís
you have a lot of support, I do it okay because it really is for another separate video because otherwise
tienes mucho apoyo lo hago vale porque es que realmente es para otro vídeo aparte porque si
this one would be on me in two hours but in short, a mother who mistreated her, a
no este se me pondría en dos horas pero vamos en resumidas cuentas una madre que la maltrató una
mother who also had a certain trauma with her daughter not growing up and tried to
madre que además tenía cierto trauma con que la hija no se hiciera mayor e intentaba por medio de
stop her physical development through food. Eh, I'm referring to the physical development so that the girls
la Alimentación frenar su desarrollo físico Eh me refiero al desarrollo físico para que a las chicas
would continue to be called from children's series, it ended up causing anorexia bulimia, the girl ended up
la siguieran llamando de series infantiles acabó provocando la anorexia bulimia la chica acabó
fatally okay, that is, the girl ended up fatally because of her mother and the little point was the director who
fatal vale o sea la chica acabó fatal por culpa de la madre y la puntillita fue el director que
had in the series that catapulted it to success, we are talking about a series with so much success that even
tuvo en la serie que la catapultó al éxito estamos hablando de una serie con tanto éxito que incluso
Michelle Obama herself, some famous models, presenters, Emma Stone, a lot of
la mismísima Michelle Obama algunos modelos famosos presentadores Emma Stone un montón de
celebrities from the elite of North America have had their cameo in this series due to the popularity it
famosos de la élite de Norteamérica han tenido su cameo dentro de esta serie de la popularidad que
had, focusing on this video. in what jenette says about dan in this book in which she never
tenía centrándonos en este vídeo en lo que cuenta jenette sobre dan en este libro en el que nunca lo
names him. By the way, every time she refers to him she calls him the creator, which is a way of calling him
nombra Por cierto Cada vez que hace alusión a él lo llama el creador que es una forma de llamarlo
in which it is clearly understood that it goes to him not only because of the context and because of the story, which
en la que se entiende de sobras que va para él no solamente por el contexto y por la historia que
is more than evident, but because in previous interviews he had already called him that To prepare
es más que evidente sino porque ya en entrevistas anteriores lo había llamado así Para ir preparando
people He states things that could belong to the field of labor abuse, such as suddenly
a la gente Afirma cosas que podrían pertenecer al ámbito del abuso laboral como de repente los
this gentleman's mood changes the same thing one day Endo was telling her that she was the best actress
cambios de humor de este caballero lo mismo un día le estaba diciendo Endo que era la mejor actriz
in the world and the next day he was yelling at her and yelling at her because she was doing her job Bad.
del mundo y al día siguiente la estaba gritando y la estaba chillando porque hacía su trabajo Mal
Even that could basically happen because it could be an episode of a bad day, I don't know, it's not to
Hasta eso básicamente podría pasar porque podría ser un episodio de un mal día no sé no es por
justify it But it's not What's serious, what's serious is this. Not at one of the dinners, the man approached her
justificarlo Pero no es lo grave lo grave es esto no en una de las cenas el hombre se acercó a ella
while she was commenting on the derivative project and touched her knees without authorization. Macardy recalled
mientras comentaba sobre el proyecto derivado y le tocó las rodillas sin autorización macardy recordó
that this touch gave her cold chills and when he realized it, he asked her if she had cold and then
que ese toque le provocó escalos fríos y que él se dio cuenta le preguntó si tenía frío y luego
covered her with his coat while he placed it on her shoulders. The creator patted her
la cubrió con su abrigo mientras se lo colocaba sobre los hombros el creador le dio palmadas
shoulders, which became a massage. He felt the ground and ended up giving her a
en los hombros que se convirtieron en masaje fue palpando el terreno y acabó haciéndole un masaje
face massage that, more than relaxing her, made her tense and on alert. But she couldn't stop him because
por la cara que más que relajarla la pusieron tensa y en alerta pero no pudo detenerlo porque
she was afraid that he would be offended. One important thing we have to say about Jenet's relationship
tenía miedo que se ofendiera una cosa importante que tenemos que decir sobre la relación de jenet
with Dam was that he had promised her on several occasions that at some point she would get
con dam era que este le había prometido en varias ocasiones que en algún momento le llegaría a ella
a series in which this role would be the protagonist. The protagonist never arrived and here we come to the
una serie en la que sería protagonista este papel de protagonista nunca llegó y aquí llegamos a la
series Sam and Cat in which not only was she not the only protagonist but her partner
serie Sam y Cat en la que no solamente no era la única protagonista sino que su compañera
with whom she co-starred in the series was none other than Ariana Grande, who was already
con la que coprotagonista la serie no era otra que Ni más ni menos Ariana Grande que ya venía
warm from Victorius, her popularity was increasing, we are talking about a girl who
calentita de Victorius su popularidad estaba incre chendo estamos hablando de una chica que
was exploiting and also had talent in music. She has already confessed on many occasions that
estaba explotando y además tenía talento en la música yan ha confesado en muchas ocasiones que
she was jealous of Ariana and the relationship between the two became more and more complicated. She
le tenía cierto celo a Ariana y la relación entre ambas se fue complicando cada vez más y más Ella
was jealous because Ariana She had certain privileges, for example, when she had another musical commitment,
tenía celo porque Ariana tenía ciertos privilegios por ejemplo cuando tenía otro compromiso musical
they even changed the script of the series and stated that her character was not around or
cambiaban Incluso el guión de la serie y afirmaban que su personaje pues no estaba estaba por ahí o
was locked in a room, something about which, for example, she complained that they did not do
Estaba encerrado en un cuarto cosa de la que por ejemplo ella se quejaba que con ella no hacían
the same with her. When she got another job that coincided with the recording of the series, she had to
igual que cuando A ella le salía otro trabajo que coincidía con la grabación de la serie tenía que
reject the other job. I really don't see anything out of this world. I see this as normal.
rechazar el otro trabajo esto yo realmente no lo veo nada del otro mundo esto lo veo que es normal
In the end, the company wanted to keep Ariana Grande, who was the musical star of the young people
al final en la empresa querían mantener a Ariana Grande que era la estrella musical de los jóvenes
of the moment and we are talking about a top artist who The later he leaves, the better for the
del momento y estamos hablando de un artista top que Cuanto más tarde se vaya mejor para la
network, according to Jannette, the straw that broke the camel's back for her to burst with jealousy is that one day
cadena según cuenta Jannette la gota que colmó el vaso para que ella estalle de celos es que un día
Ariana Grande arrives at the studio commenting that he's been out last night playing charades
Ariana Grande llega al estudio comentando que ha estado la noche anterior jugando a las charadas
at tom's house HK from then on i didn't like him i couldn't like the success of a
en la casa de Tom HK a partir de ese momento no me cayó bien no podía caerme bien el éxito de una
pop star i could handle it but hanging out with sheriff bodyy with fucking forest
estrella del pop podía manejarlo pero pasar el rato con el sheriff bodyy con el maldito Forest
gum This had gone too far, I swear, when I read this sentence I think it's a joke.
gum esto había ido demasiado lejos te lo juro que yo Cuando leo esta frase me creo que es de broma
but not really, the bad vibes between the two were palpable in the atmosphere according to
pero realmente no realmente el mal rollo entre las dos se palpaba en el ambiente según la revista
people magazine, the series that you 35 chapters was canceled since the work environment between Jenette and
people la serie que tú 35 capítulos se canceló ya que el ambiente de trabajo entre jenette y
Ariana was completely unsustainable and after Ariana decided not to continue in a new
Ariana era completamente insostenible y después de que Ariana decidió no continuar en una nueva
season the series was canceled here you have the tweet with which Ariana Grande said goodbye to the
temporada la serie fue cancelada aquí tenéis el tweet con el que Ariana Grande se despidió de la
audience of the series I am not going to read it for obvious reasons a lot of text ok I am going to pass it
audiencia de la serie no lo voy a leer por razones obvias muchísimo texto vale lo voy a ir pasando
down like this in case you want to stop the video and want read it yourself but let's go basically here
así para abajo por si queréis parar el vídeo y queréis leerlo ustedes pero vamos básicamente aquí
what catches my attention is that he says goodbye to the entire team he says goodbye to the entire audience he says
lo que me llama la atención es que se despide de todo el equipo se despide de toda la audiencia se
goodbye to dan having nice words for him but he doesn't make any mention of his partner the co
despide de dan teniendo una bonitas palabras para él pero no hace ninguna mención a su compañera la
-star of the series and It is not precisely because the tweet does not fit. This is what is
coprotagonista de la serie y no es precisamente porque no le quepa el tweet Esto es lo que se
called a longer tweet. Previously, when Twitter Blue was not paid, it was a thing that
llama un tweet longer que anteriormente cuando no se pagaba el Twitter Blue era una cosa que
was used so that you could post a very long tweet. Come on, it was a link and you wrote the
se utilizaba para que tú pudieras poner un tweet larguísimo vamos era un enlace y tú escribías el
long one . text within the link, according to Janette, the program's production team
mucho texto dentro del enlace según ha contado Janette el equipo de producción del programa le
offered her 300,000 so that she would never speak again about the mistreatment and alleged abuses that
ofreció 300,000 para que nunca jamás hablase de los malos tratos y de los supuestos abusos que
she had suffered while she had been working with them, something that Jenes did not agree
habría pasado mientras que había estado trabajando con ellos algo con lo que jenes no estuvo de
with and he didn't accept the money what the hell or that the deon is offering me 0000,000 in money so
acuerdo y no aceptó la pasta qué diablos ni que l deon me está ofreciendo 0000,000 en dinero para
that I don't speak publicly about my experience on the program my personal experience of the
que no hable públicamente sobre mi experiencia en el programa mi experiencia personal del abuso
creator's abuse This is a network with programs made for children they shouldn't have any type of
del creador Esta es una red con programas hechas para niños no deberían tener algún tipo de brújula
moral compass, shouldn't they at least try to report some type of ethical standard, the most controversial thing about
moral no deberían al menos tratar de reportar algún tipo de estándar ético lo más polémico de
their book is the headline I'm glad my mom died but I'm telling you, it's so much of a topic that it gives me for
su libro el titular Me alegro de que mi mamá murió pero ya os digo es tanto el tema que me da para
another video So if you want it Proving it to me, the Ariana Grande thing that I already told you, makes me
otro vídeo Así que si lo queréis demostrármelo el tema de Ariana Grande que ya os digo me escama
very nervous. The truth is that I don't understand this girl's reaction and once she has nothing to do
muchísimo La verdad es que no entiendo la reacción de esta chica y ya una vez no teniendo nada que
with Nickelodion, I don't know if it's out of gratitude because they are the ones who catapulted her and the that
ver con nickelodion no sé si es en agradecimiento porque sean los que la han catapultado y los que
they have given her the showcase so that she is where she is today but basically Well, before working
le han dado el escaparate para que hoy esté donde esté pero básicamente Bueno ella antes de trabajar
with them she had like a lot of spam tweets trying to get the attention of the creator of
con ellos tenía como muchos tweets spameando intentando llamar la atención del creador de
Dan snake neider And well, not only that but she had a lot of affectionate tweets with him
Dan snake neider Y bueno pues no solamente eso sino que tenía muchos tweets cariñosos con él
Already working at the network, in fact in 2017 he asked Dan to see if he could bring together the casting
ya trabajando en la cadena de hecho en 2017 le pidió a dan que a ver si podía reunir al casting
of the Victorius series to make a special Something to which Dan responded that it was in them
de la serie de Victorius para hacer un especial Algo a lo que dan respondió que estaba en ellos
and that he would try and that he would do everything possible and well, she followed him on her Twitter account until the
y que lo intentaría y que Haría todo lo posible y bueno lo siguió en su cuenta de Twitter hasta el
day she deleted the account on her Instagram account, we can see that she continues to follow him and I'm
día que ella se eliminó la cuenta en su cuenta de Instagram podemos ver que le sigue siguiendo y ya
telling you, I imagine it will be as a thank you But I don't understand this defense but neither for her nor
os digo me imagino que será como en agradecimiento Pero no entiendo esta defensa pero ni por ella ni
by his colleagues A manda vines was the first victim of dan sneider his show his program was his
por sus compañeros A manda vines fue la primera víctima de dan sneider su show su programa fue su
first success as a writer and as a producer he discovered her doing comedy in an audition and since
primer éxito como escritor y como productor é la descubrió haciendo comedia en una audición y desde
then he had his eye on her and knew that the girl would be a star we are speaking of 1998 and in '99
entonces le echó el ojo y supo que la chica sería una estrella estamos hablando de 1998 y en el 99
he created a series for her where she was the star, in fact the program even had her name and he spent
le creó una serie donde ella era estrella de hecho el programa tenía incluso su nombre y pasaba con
a lot of time with her because as he said they shared the same type of humor and got along very well the
ella mucho tiempo porque según decía compartían el mismo tipo de humor y se llevaban muy bien the
deting up Heaven Looking down saying I think her a challenge dan Saw her and like immediately knew
deting up Heaven Looking down saying I think her a challeng dan Saw her and like immediately knew
she'd be a Star he recognizes her Talent and he wants her on all that immediately
she'd be a Star he recognizes her Talent and he wants her on all that immediately
mea
mea
you Yes H to I think win rare rare to say the least she even tried to emancipate herself from her
you Yes H to I think win rarito rarito cuanto menos ella incluso intentó emanciparse de sus
parents to not having to ask their permission to make any agreement that arose with Dan,
padres para no tener que pedirles permiso para hacer cualquier acuerdo que le surgiese con dan
however, over the years, when she grew older and had a
sin embargo la chica con el paso de los años cuando fue haciéndose mayor y encadena con un
lot of problems, she ended up involved in drugs and ended up with mental problems. The girl ended up in
montón de problemas acabó metida en las drogas acabó con problemas mentales la chica acabó en
a state of Similar to what happened to Britney, but I'm talking to you about a state of
un estado parecido a lo que le pasó a Britney peer os estoy hablando de un estado de salud
mental health that when they declare that everything, including your decisions, is handed over to your
mental que cuando te declaran en él todo incluso tus decisiones pasan a mano de tus
guardians, the girl even caused a fire in the middle of the street, that is, the girl Lio
tutores la chica incluso provocó un incendio en medio de la calle o sea la chica la Lio
písac level britne p so that you understand me very similar everything in fact almost the same and of
písac nivel britne p para que me entendáis muy parecido todo de hecho casi igual y de
Suddenly, apparently, she began to realize all the abuse that, according to her, she would have suffered
repente por lo visto empezó a darse cuenta de todos los abusos que según ella habría sufrido
from Dam. From her Twitter account, she would have published things like this. Give me one and I
por parte de dam desde su cuenta de Twitter habría publicado cosas como estas Dame un y
will give you a show. Sneider, see me and I will put you in Nikelodion, that is, they fixed it What she says in
te daré un show sneider vesa mi y te meto en nikelodion o sea fijaron lo que pone en
the tweets is also directly mentioning Dan's last name, that is,
los tweets además mencionando directamente el apellido de dan o sea lo está señalando
she is pointing it out directly. They took away her Twitter account. I think the parents wanted to avoid
directamente le quitaron la cuenta de Twitter creo que los padres querían evitar problemas
legal problems or something like that and she created another account again where she posted similar things
legales o algo por el estilo y ella se volvió a hacer otra cuenta donde puso cosas similares
. many rumors in Hollywood some real and some false one man in particular took hundreds
hay muchos rumores en Hollywood algunos reales y otros falsos un hombre en particular tomó cientos
of photos of my feet I was 13 years old and that is one of the main reasons why I don't want
de fotos de mis pies tenía 13 años y esa es una de las principales razones por las que no quiero
to get pregnant Maybe this time he is not mentioning my last name dan dan sneider
quedar embarazada A lo mejor en esta ocasión no está mencionando el apellido de dan dan sneider
but who do you think these tweets are alluding to, most likely the weirdo with the
pero a quién creéis que estos tweet está haciendo alusión pues muy probablemente al rarito de los
feet nurses these Kid Feet Hello This is dan Schneider aka dan warp on Twitter
pies nurses these Kid Feet Hello This is dan Schneider aka dan warp on Twitter
here niel Where no Open Shoes or sandals are allowed on stage we're
here niel Where no Open Shoes or sandals are allow on stage we're
This girl that you are seeing on the screen is called Alexa Nicolás and she is one of the actresses of Soy 101.
esta chica que estáis viendo en pantalla se llama Alexa Nicolás y es una de las actrices de soy 101
This girl accused Dan that Dan made her model in his cting and in the tests with skirts that were too
esta chica acusó a dan de que dan la hacía modelar en su cting y en las pruebas con faldas demasiado
short, so short that the shorts that she wore you know that sometimes when
cortas tan cortas que los short que ella se ponía debajo ya sabéis no que algunas veces cuando las
girls put on a miniskirt, to keep everything under control, they put on shorts underneath because
chicas se ponen minifalda pues para tenerlo todo controlado pues se ponen unos pantaloncitos debajo
I said that these shorts even had to be cut so that they wouldn't show how
pues decía que estos pantaloncitos se los tenía incluso que cortar para que no se vieran de lo
short the skirts actually were. Here I will be putting a text on the screen of
cortas que eran las faldas de hecho por aquí os estaré poniendo un texto en pantalla de
his statement dan He even kept the photographs in which Alexa modeled the outfit
su declaración dan Incluso se quedaba con las fotografías en las que Alexa modelaba el outfit
to the point that he would sit in the chair and I would go out and do a little turn Sneider looked
hasta el punto que él se sentaba en la silla y yo salía y daba un pequeño giro sneider miraba
at the costume artist And she said I can keep the Polaroid God God Apparently this girl
al artista de vestuario Y decía puedo quedarme la Polaroid Dios Dios Al parecer esta chica también
has also reported episodes of bullying by her colleagues in the series and that Dan allowed it and
ha contado episodios de bullying por parte de los compañeros de la serie y que dan lo permitía y
Dan's and Nickelodeon's lawyers contacted the girl and her family in 2019
los abogados de dan y Nickelodeon se pusieron en contacto con la chica y con su familia en 2019
to warn her to be quiet dan at Me Do you understand called zo 101 and Nicole 10 and
para advertirle de que estuviera callada dan at Me Do you understand called zo 101 and Nicole 10 and
lik Alexa comments that she was even once pushed towards a rock just before
lik Alexa comenta que incluso una vez fue empujada hacia una roca justo antes de
starting a scene by none other than christin Herrera who has the
comenzar una escena por nada más y nada menos que christin Herrera quien tiene el papel de
on they called action and like they're running toward you know Whatever and so I cried to My
de on they called action and like they're running toward you know Whatever and so I cried to My
Mom afterwards letting her know what happened and She Let the producers know but unfortunately they did
Mom afterwards letting her know what happened and She Let the producers know but unfortunately they
n't care basically and you know he tried to get me to um Sign something you know in 2019 And I was
didn't care basically and you know he tried to get me to um Sign something you know in 2019 And I was
like yeah What do you want and he goes well we've heard you've been speaking out about dan then he
like yeah What do you want and he goes well we've heard youve been speaking out about dan then he
goes dan and I would like to have you come into a room and come up with some, as I already told you
goes dan and I would like to have you come into a room and come up with some como ya os he comentado
at the beginning of the video, Dan had hired three men in his work team at the network
al principio del vídeo dan tenía contratados en la cadena en su equipo de trabajo a tres hombres
who were convicted of pedophilia and even when accusations and suspicions began to arise, Dan
que fueron condenados por pedofilia e incluso cuando empezaron a ha acusaciones y sospechas dan
Schneider continued to keep him on his team, he is the case for example of this man Jason Michael
Schneider lo siguió manteniendo en su equipo es el caso por ejemplo de este hombre Jason Michael
handy this pedophile assistant of dan sneider's production team made friends with
handy este pedófilo asistente del equipo de producción de dan sneider se hacía amigo de
the girls on the set and then sent them images of his private parts by email
las niñas del set y luego les enviaba imágenes de sus partes íntimas por correo electrónico
was J Let was
was J Let was
innocent you have to be sick by now to think
inocent que ya tienes que estar enfermo para pensar
that they are not even going to catch you doing that when we are talking about very
que ni siquiera te van a pillar haciendo eso cuando estamos hablando de niñas muy
minor girls
menores
c and said got emil jas was of him naked masturbating and he said Had sent to her
c and said got emil jas was of him naked masturbating and he said Had sent to her
Because her to See That he wasing of her this pedophile I insist condemned him They found notes
Because her to See That he wasing of her este pedófilo insisto condenado le encontraron notas
in which he commented on a kind of diary How he had kissed a
en las que comentaba una especie de diario Cómo había besado muchas veces a una chiquilla de
9-year-old girl many times. They found bags with a lot of photos of little girls and after the
9 años le encontraron bolsas con un montón de fotos de niñas pequeñas y después de la
first accusation they took a while to fire him. In other words, they didn't fire him immediately and then
primera acusación tardaron en despedirlo O sea no lo despidieron de inmediato y luego
we have this guy Brian pck Brian pak was arrested in 2003 for sexual abuse sodomy
tenemos a este tipo Brian pck Brian pak fue arrestado en 2003 por abuso sexual sodomia
and oral copulation of minors under 16 years of age to several minors one of these victims' names
y cópula oral a menores de 16 años a varios menores uno de estos nombres de las víctimas
was kept anonymous and today with this documentary it has been discovered that he was
se mantuvo en el anonimato y hoy con con este documental se ha descubierto que era
one of the most important actors of the network the protagonist of the series Drake
uno de los actores más importantes de la cadena el protagonista de la serie Drake
Bell and Twitter that night tm pap there on the
Bell and Twitter that night tm pap there on the
day of sentencing bri to the courth the most unbelievable
day of sentencing bri to the courth the most unbelievable
Thing there were definitely some recognizable faces on that side of the room And My Side
Thing there were definitely some recognizable faces on that side of the room And My Side
was uh Me My mom and my brother Brian Had been convicted but Getting All of this Support from
was uh Me My mom and my brother Brian Had been convicted but Getting All of this Support from
a lot of people in the Industry And I was Pretty shocked I addressed my statement to everyone in
a lot of people in the Industry And I was Pretty shocked I addressed my statement to everyone in
the room I looked at All of them And I just said How dare you and I said You Will forever
the room I looked at All of them And I just said How dare you and I said You Will forever
have the Memory of sitting in this courtroom and defending this person And I will forever
have the Memory of sitting in this courtroom and defending this person And I will forever
brutal without words family without words And this guy at least is in prison but let there be people
brutal sin palabras familia sin palabras Y este tío por lo menos está preso pero que haya gente
in this story who leave from Rosita I think it's an incredible family, here we go
en esta historia que se vaya de Rosita Me parece increíble familia por aquí vamos
leaving today's video I hope you liked it Although what we have
dejando el videíto de hoy Espero que haya sido de vuestro agrado Aunque lo que hemos contado
obviously told on this occasion have not been pleasant things but that is what we have to inform you of,
evidentemente en esta ocasión no han sido cosas agradables pero es lo que nos toca para informaros
we will be attentive to any new information that This video comes out, let's say that it has been
estaremos pendientes de cualquier información nueva que salga Este vídeo digamos que ha sido
like the context But there are many stories to tell, in fact I have already told you that if you want
como el contexto Pero hay muchas historias que contar de hecho ya os he dicho que si queréis
the video where I tell you Janette's story, ask me for it And if I see that it is going to be worth it, I
el vídeo donde os cuente la historia de Janette me lo pedís Y si veo que va a merecer la pena os
will do it. forget to subscribe to the Channel don't forget to give me a like if you liked
lo hago no olvidéis suscribiros al Canal no olvidéis regalarme un like si os ha gustado
the video I will be reading the comment box Let's see what you think about this whole topic above
el vídeo estaré leyendo la caja de comentarios A veris qué opináis sobre todo este tema sobre
all I ask you to share it strongly so that this topic is not forgotten
todo Os pido que lo compartáis fuertemente para que este tema no quede en el olvido
and anything Let's see a gorgeous kiss bye until the next video
y cualquier cosa nos vamos viendo un beso guapísimos chao hasta el siguiente videíto
ah
ah